<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Katherine Piatti on Home</title>
    <link>https://katherinepiatti.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Katherine Piatti on Home</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://katherinepiatti.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How I Built THIS Website</title>
      <link>https://katherinepiatti.com/blog/my_website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://katherinepiatti.com/blog/my_website/</guid>
      <description>Several people have asked for the resources I used to create this website. I&amp;rsquo;m writing this so I can just send a link when responding to any future requests.
The three main criteria I used when choosing what tools to use:
 Quick &amp;amp; easy enough to learn that I could have a basic site up and running within a day or two and add/update content without too much effort.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credit Risk Assessment with Python</title>
      <link>https://katherinepiatti.com/post/creditone_project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://katherinepiatti.com/post/creditone_project/</guid>
      <description>The prescribed objective for this project was to outline and then implement a data science process—like CRISP-DM—resulting in a model that could reliably predict whether or not a customer would default on their loan(s) from their demographic information, as well as six months worth of data on their billing and payment history.
#import required packages from sqlalchemy import create_engine import pymysql import pandas as pd import numpy as np  Obtain Data The CreditOne data is on the MySQL sever, so I need to connect to the server, query the database, extract the data and export it as a .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer Purchasing Patterns (Python)</title>
      <link>https://katherinepiatti.com/post/customer_purchasing_analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://katherinepiatti.com/post/customer_purchasing_analysis/</guid>
      <description>The purpose of this project was to learn how to use Anaconda, Python, Jupyter Lab, and version control/reproducibility practices and tools such as virtual environments, Git, and GitHub while analyzing a dataset of customer demographic and transaction information from an regional electronics retailer.
 Data Wrangling Getting the raw data ready for analysis is typically an intensive, time consuming process. However, the raw data for this project was already in good shape when I got it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Energy Consumption Analysis (R)</title>
      <link>https://katherinepiatti.com/post/submeter_energy_analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://katherinepiatti.com/post/submeter_energy_analysis/</guid>
      <description>The goal of this project is to analyze energy consumption data over a three year span to provide evidence (if possible) supporting a client&amp;rsquo;s claim that their residence was unoccupied during the summer (June-August) of 2008.
 Dataset Info The energy consumption data is from January 2007 through December 2009 and was gathered from 3 submeters in a single family home located in Sceaux, France (nearly 2 million data points). Each submeter monitors energy consumption in a different area of the house:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume | Contact</title>
      <link>https://katherinepiatti.com/resume_contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://katherinepiatti.com/resume_contact/</guid>
      <description>   [Download PDF]
 Contact Me Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
